# **Nathaniel Barrera**

# General Engineering Student

Engineering student with 4 years of customer service looking to develop skills related to software architecture and programming as an intern, as well as further building upon soft skills related toward team building and social interaction.

#### Contact

#### Address

Round Rock, TX, 78664

#### Phone

(512) 584-0031

#### E-mail

nathaniel.barrera39@gmail.co m

#### LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com /in/nathaniel-barrera-2587

## Skills

- Emphasizes listening over speaking during conversations.
- Remains Calm in stressful environments.
- Practices empathy and understands multiple perspectives

# Accomplishments

- Eagle Scout January 2016
- Chevron Engineering
  Mentorship Program 2022

## **Projects**

- Connect 4

## Education

#### 2022-08 -Current

## Bachelor of Science: General Engineering

Texas A&M University - College Station, TX Relevant Courses:

ENGR-102 (Python3)

#### 2016-08 -2023-05

## Associate of Science: Computer Science

Austin Community College - Austin, TX Relevant Courses:

- Programming Fundamentals 1 (Python3)
- Programming Fundamentals 2 (C++)
- Programming Fundamentals 3 (C++)
- · Machine Learning

# Work History

#### 2020-05 -Current

## Material Fulfillment Specialist

Bare Performance Nutrition, Round Rock, Texas

- Collaborated with departments across the company, including marketing and project management, in creating new ideas, initiatives, products, and services.
- Developed and maintained relationships with 10 new staff members, and focused on creating core conversational and resolution skills.
- Ensures time is made for each item ordered is sent correctly to ensure customer satisfaction.

## 2016-08 -2020-06

## Central Service Cashier

H-E-B, Round Rock, Texas

- Provided unique customer service skills, keeping customers engaged and satisfied.
- Engaged with customers to ensure they found the item they were looking for.
- demonstrated attention to detail and patience by resolving customer's issues.

# Hobbies

- Enjoys collecting and listening to vinyl records.
- Makes time to go to the gym to be in my thoughts.
- Loves being up to date with tech and seeing how much technology improves over time.